# **Bagas Prasetyo Nugroho**

Blitar, Indonesia | Phone: (+62)855 4611 1091 | Email: bagasprenzo@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a fresh graduated of ITN Malang, I am a UI/UX Designer with +2 years of experience. I am Familiar with research, prototyping, designing sketches, design thinking, flow diagrams, wireframes, mockup. Proven to increase application effectiveness and design of the developed application and website

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### UI Designer - Malang, Indonesia

Freelance (April 2021 – July 2021)

- Create User Interface design website
- Create Logo company

### UI/UX Designer - Malang, Indonesia

Lowokwaru sub-district office (May 2022 - Agust 2022)

- Create User Interface and User Experience design website
- Create concept design website
- Usability testing fiture website

### UI Designer - Malang, Indonesia

Freelance (November 2022 - January 2023)

• Create User Interface design application mobile

## **Project ( Portofolio )**

### • UI/UX Design Bimbel Online | Final Project | 2021

- Create UI/UX Design as a platform website Bimbel Online in Malang, Indonesia. Application Design were made using: Figma, AdobeXD
- Link Project : https://dribbble.com/bagas\_prasetyo

## UI/UX Design Food Restaurant Website | Final Project | 2021

- Create UI/UX Design as a platform Bimbel Online Website in Malang, Indonesia. Application Design were made using: Figma, AdobeXD
- Link Project : https://dribbble.com/bagas\_prasetyo

## • UI Design Payment Website | Freelance Project | 2022

- Create UI Design as a platform Payment Website in Malang, Indonesia.

  Application Design were made using: Figma, AdobeXD, Miro, Maze, Adobe Ilustator
- Link Project : https://dribbble.com/bagas\_prasetyo

### • UI/UX Design Sistem Informasi Website Lowokwaru sub-district | Final Project | 2022

- Create UI/UX Design as a platform Sistem Informasi Website in Malang, Indonesia. Application Design were made using : Figma, AdobeXD, Miro, Adobe Ilustator, InVision
- Link Project : <a href="https://dribbble.com/bagas\_prasetyo">https://dribbble.com/bagas\_prasetyo</a>

### • UI Design Ticketing App | Freelance Project | 2022

- Create UI Design as a Ticketing App in Malang, Indonesia.
   Application Design were made using: Figma, AdobeXD, InVision, Adobe Ilustator, Miro
- Link Project : https://dribbble.com/bagas\_prasetyo

#### **EDUCATION**

### **NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY MALANG (2019 - 2023)**

S1 - Informatics Engineering - GPA 3.68 / 4.00

## **SKILLS & TOOLS**

- Skills: UI/UX Design, Grapihc Design, Logo Design, Kotlin, JavaScript, SQL, Firebase C++, HTML & CSS, Internet of Thing (IoT)
- Tools: Figma, Adobe (Adobe XD, photoshop, illustator), Miro, Maze, InVision App, CorelDRAW, Android Studio, Visual Studio Code, MySQL, Firebase, Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Power Point, Access)